Caucus of Connecticut Democrats Records
© 2011 University of Connecticut
Caucus of Connecticut Democrats Records.
undated, 1960s-1993.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center
Caucus of Connecticut Democrats.
7.8 linear feet.
MSS19990081
The collection contains documentation of the organization and its activities from the 1970s through the early 1990s.
History
A New Haven, Connecticut, based organization that supports Democratic activities in Connecticut.
Scope and Content
The collection contains administrative and financial information as well as materials documenting the organization's activities from the 1960s through the early 1990s.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged as received.
Series I: Inventory ( undated, 1960s-1993 )
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to Connecticut politics. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Organizations:
Caucus of Connecticut Democrats.
Subjects:
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Administrative Records.; Financial Records.; Minutes.; Fliers. [printed matter]; Photocopies.; Notes.; Newspapers.; Photographs.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
The materials were donated by Edith Baron in August 1999.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Inventory, undated, 1960s-1993
  - Mary Sullivan, Chair, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Legislative Electoral Action Program material, undated
  - Human Rights/Opportunities/Services, undated
  - Justice/Law Enforcement/Civil Liberties (including ACLU-CCLU), undated
  - National Committee, undated
  - Labor, undated
  - Delegate Selection NDC, undated
  - State Convention, 1972
  - Mental Health (including Mental Health Association of Connecticut), undated
  - NDC Center to Save the Reforms, undated
  - Welfare Rights, undated
  - Public Interest Lobby, undated
  - Unidentified, 1979
  - Elections, 1972
  - Elections, 1973
  - Elections, 1970
  - Elections, 1968
  - Election Law/Reform, 1969, 1973
  - Fiscal Policy (Documents), undated
  - Fiscal Policy, 1969
  - General Assembly (general), undated
  - General Assembly, 1969
  - General Assembly, 1972
  - General Assembly, 1973
  - Housing and Urban Affairs, undated
  - Elections, 1978
  - Correspondence - Committee for an Effective Legislature Board, 1978
  - Forum: Conn and Economic Crisis, 1975 March
  - NDC Platforms, 1972, 1976, 1978
  - Citizens Task Force on the Future of Connecticut's Economy, undated
  - Connecticut Citizens Action Group, undated
  - Consumer Protection, undated
  - Education, undated
  - Environmental Protection, undated
  - Foreign Policy & Military Spending, undated
  - CCD Treasurer, undated
  - Information, Primary Election, 1978 (Box 2)
  - CCD, 1976
  - Committee for an Effective Legislature 1978 Administration, undated
  - Party Rules/Reforms, undated
  - Multinational Corps, undated, 1975 April
  - Mini Nat's Convent CCCD delegate challenge, 1978
  - CCD National Platform, 1979
  - CEL - 1974 Legislature, undated
  - Campaign Finance, undated
  - CCD Board, 1979-1980
  - Abortion Reform, undated
  - Americans for Democratic Action, undated
  - Treasurer's Report, undated
  - 10th Anniversary/History, undated
  - 20th Anniversary Dinner, undated
  - Issues--Old, undated
  - CCD Board, 1972-1973
  - Executive Committee, 1973-1974
  - Executive Committee, 1975
  - CCD Board, 1976-1977
  - CCD Board, 1977-1978
  - CCD Board, 1978-1979
  - Constitution & Bylaws, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Notes, correspondence, administrative records, financial records, clippings, ephemeras, books, fliers, publication, 1970-1980
    [Subjects include: Committee/Board, administrative matters.]
  - Fliers, correspondence, clippings, notes, administrative records, publications, poster, undated, 1970-1993 (Box 4)
    [Subjects include: Administration, committees, events, public relations.]
  - Administrative records, financial records, correspondence, notes, clippings, ephemera, fliers, photographs, publication, undated, 1970-1991 (Box 5)
    [Subjects include: Committee records, administrative/financial report, programs, public relations.]
  - Financial and administrative records, fliers, publications, clippings, correspondence, notes, ephemera, undated, 1970s-1990s (Box 6)
    [Subjects include: Activities and public relations.]